Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ronlouie-abadecio-33731428a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
Visual Storytelling

Storytelling
YouTube Video Creation

Ronlouie Abadecio

Creative Short-form Video Editor | Collaborating with entrepreneurs, creatives, and business proprietors to enhance engagement through video | Slide into my DMs!

Valenzuela, National Capital Region, Philippines

Summary

Hey! I'm Ronlouie Abadecio, a passionate freelance video editor specialize in creating visually stunning and engaging videos that captivate audience. My journey into video editing started since 2019 as a hobby, a way to express myself creatively. But as I immersed myself in the craft, I discovered it's about more than just putting clips together. It's about seizing moments, stirring emotions, and making a lasting impression.

With each project using Adobe Premiere Pro, I dive deeper into my passion, pushing my creative limits, playing with effects and transitions, and refining my skills with every edit.

Throughout my career, I've become really good at making different types of videos: Talking Head, Podcast Clips, Documentary, Reels(B-rolls) and Social Media Contents. But the best part about video editing for me is turning my creative ideas into awesome videos.

If you're looking for a video editor, Let's collaborate and create something extraordinary together. Whether you're a small business looking to boost your online presence or a content creator in need of a skilled editor, I'm here to help. Contact me today, and let's turn your ideas into reality!!!

Experience

Vandalist
Freelance Video Editor
March 2024 - Present (10 months)
Stones Corner, Queensland

Saliksik Investigative

Video Editor

September 2023 - December 2023 (4 months)

Philippines

- Performed video editing services for true to life crime stories videos
- Created video using visual storytelling

OnlineJobs.PH Freelance Video Editor March 2022 - 2023 (1 year) Philippines

Upwork Video Editor March 2021 - 2023 (2 years) Philippines

Education

ACLC College

Associate's degree, Computer Technology/Computer Systems Technology · (2021 - 2023)